<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>52-Ancestors on Wheeler Genealogy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/52-ancestors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 52-Ancestors on Wheeler Genealogy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2026 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/52-ancestors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Kinney (52 Ancestors; #3 Andrew Kinney, Sr.)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/20/andrew-kinney-52-ancestors-%233-andrew-kinney-sr./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/20/andrew-kinney-52-ancestors-%233-andrew-kinney-sr./</guid>
      <description>I am extremely fortunate that my family has been able to preserve some fantastic family photos. One such photo is that of Andrew Kinney (or photos). You may recall that we introduced Sylvester Beasecker (52 Ancestors, #2) who married Katharine Kinney (b. 11 Oct 1869, d. 23 Dec 1912) about 1896 in Pennsylvania. Katharine Kinney’s parents were Andrew Kinney and Margaret McTavish.
Andrew Kinney was born about 1823 in Ireland. We have only been able to identify the approximate birth date and location for Andrew Kinney based upon census records, voter registration and death records. Andrew passed away 22 May 1900 in Chicago, Cook, Illinois. We know from an article in The Commonwealth published in Fond du Lac, Wisconsin that Andrew’s birth year is about 1823 based upon the age cited in the article. The article states that Andrew’s remains arrived from Chicago after Andrew passed away in his home located at 424 Park Avenue in Chicago.
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Kinney (52 Ancestors; #3 Andrew Kinney, Sr.)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/19/andrew-kinney-52-ancestors-3-andrew-kinney-sr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/19/andrew-kinney-52-ancestors-3-andrew-kinney-sr/</guid>
      <description>I am extremely fortunate that my family has been able to preserve some fantastic family photos. One such photo is that of Andrew Kinney (or photos). You may recall that we introduced Sylvester Beasecker (52 Ancestors, #2) who married Katharine Kinney (b. 11 Oct 1869, d. 23 Dec 1912) about 1896 in Pennsylvania. Katharine Kinney’s parents were Andrew Kinney and Margaret McTavish.
Andrew Kinney was born about 1823 in Ireland. We have only been able to identify the approximate birth date and location for Andrew Kinney based upon census records, voter registration and death records. Andrew passed away 22 May 1900 in Chicago, Cook, Illinois. We know from an article in The Commonwealth published in Fond du Lac, Wisconsin that Andrew’s birth year is about 1823 based upon the age cited in the article. The article states that Andrew’s remains arrived from Chicago after Andrew passed away in his home located at 424 Park Avenue in Chicago.
</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martha Beasecker (52 Ancestors: #1 Martha Ann Bowman Beasecker)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/05/martha-beasecker-52-ancestors-%231-martha-ann-bowman-beasecker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/01/05/martha-beasecker-52-ancestors-%231-martha-ann-bowman-beasecker/</guid>
      <description>I began genealogy shortly after the passing of my Aunt Hazel who, to the best of my knowledge, was one of the only people in the Wheeler line doing any kind of genealogy. Not long after getting started, and with family pictures, I became interested in the life and history of my great-grandfather Sylvester Beasecker (b. 06 Feb 1859; d. 01 May 1933).
Sylvester is the son of Samuel Beasecker (b. 13 Feb 1831 in Montgomery, Ohio; d. 06 Jun 1888 in Goshen, Elkhart, Indiana). According to the International Marriage Records, 1560 - 1900, Samuel married Martha Browen born in Pennsylvania in 1836. Numerous searches for Martha Browen in and out of Pennsylvania yielded very little in regards to the background of Martha. Eventually I came across the death record for Martha (as well as several other Beaseckers) in South Bend, Indiana and she was buried in Sugar Grove Cemetery in Goshen, Indiana. On a trip from Illinois to Michigan, I made a detour and stopped by Sugar Grove Cemetery.
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
