<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myfamilydna on Wheeler Genealogy</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/myfamilydna/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Myfamilydna on Wheeler Genealogy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2026 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/myfamilydna/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Ancestry DNA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/02/ancestry-dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/03/02/ancestry-dna/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, in 2005, when I was first getting into genealogy I was excite to learn that DNA was being used to help family historians determine their background and get in contact with people that shared common Ancestors. I immediately found FamilyTreeDNA and requested a 37-marker test. I received the results and joined the “Wheeler” project.
In 2005, using DNA for genealogy was extremely new and unless you had some experience with the technology or you had someone to interpret the results for you, the value of DNA may have been limited. I was able to make contact with several individuals that I matched in the Wheeler Surname Project but it didn’t live up to my expectations. In 2008, I upgraded from 37 to 63 markers. I experienced similar results to that of my original results in that I had received results but how to use them and get in touch with others was limited. I reached out to a number of people that I had reported matches but many of them maintained paper records or family trees in GEDCOM format offline. In most cases I was unable to determine the shared ancestor.
</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
